Scott Gangemi

Hey there,

I'm a full stack developer and I'm passionate about building cool applications, and seeing the impact of awesome work.

My favourite thing about software development is creating fantastic experiences that people will love, and want to keep coming back to.





Call me 0431 987 232



or don't.
s.gangemi@me.com



scottgangemi.com github.com/Gangezilla

Experience

Domain Feb 2018 - Now Javascript Developer (Full Stack)

My key accomplishment has been to transition to Full Stack Developer, working across React and Node codebases.

 Work on server side microservices to present data to React pages.

Domain Apr 2017 - Feb 2018 Front End Developer

- Worked to upgrade Domain's listings pages to React and transitioning away from a legacy monolith code base.
- Built, worked with, and refactored React components.

APG & Co. 2016 - Now Junior Web Developer

Some of my teams favourite accomplishments were:

- Redesigned our bloated six page checkout into a sleek one page wonder.
- Tore out all of our old CSS and converted it to SASS (cutting off 300kb in the process).
- Rewrote thousands of lines of mystery JavaScript into easy to understand React.

Volunteering

NodeGirls

I've mentored and taught at NodeGirls a number of times and have:

- Mentored individuals in an Express class.
- Helped to organise and run a React workshop.

Education

UTS

2012 - 2015

Bachelor of Integrated Product Design: Major in Interaction Design

Skills

I'm really comfortable with:

- HTML
- React
- CSS
- Express
- JavaScript
- Node

I'm currently working on:

- Python
- C#
- Learning computer science fundamentals
- Building stuff and learning new things.